2go.im 2019-08-10

# 2go - Privacy

### 2GO PRIVACY NOTICE AND TERMS OF SERVICE

2go Interactive (Pty) Ltd ("2go") enables you to chat and share on your mobile phone through downloading and using the software application known as 2go and by offering you the use of this software and all and any 2go services, websites, content, products and/or virtual currency (collectively and individually referred to as the "2go Service" or the "Service").

YOUR PRIVACY IS VERY IMPORTANT TO US AND INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU WILL BE STORED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY USING THE 2GO SERVICE YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE TO 2GO'S PRIVACY POLICY AND THESE TERMS OF SERVICE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ANY OF THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICE.

### Information Collected by 2go

In order to provide you with the 2go Service, 2go collects and uses your personal information and you hereby consent to your personal information as described more fully below ("personal information") being collected, processed and/or used when using the 2go Service.

### Personally Identifiable Information

As part of your activation and use of the 2go Service you may provide certain personally identifiable information to 2go, including without limitation your name, cellular telephone number, your phone address book, gender, age, education, photos and relationship status. In addition, personal information may include any information in messages sent on the Service, including any text or photo messages exchanged between friends and/or shared in chat rooms (which are generally public). Users on 2go may also see certain of this personal information and such information may also be accessible to and used by 2go as outlined in this notice.

Please always keep your personal information private and never share GoCredits or personal information such as your telephone number with third parties, including any persons that you have met on 2go. 

### Information Shared by 2go

2go uses your personal information to provide the features and functionality of the 2go Service and to continuously operate, maintain and improve the Service. Personal information that you voluntarily disclose or share with any friends on the Service may be collected and/or used by us. Please also be aware that any such voluntarily disclosed information may be distributed by such users through the Internet or other channels and may be displayed to the general public.

### Cookies and Log Files

When you use the 2go Service we may send cookies to your browser and/or our servers may automatically log (record) certain information sent, for instance whenever you send messages or add any friends to the Service. Log files may include, without limitation, information such as your IP address, browser type, phone type, your mobile carrier, location, the date and time of your messages or friend requests, your phone number and/or phone number/s of friends on the Service.

### Personally Identifiable Information

2go does not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for their commercial use without your prior consent or except if we give the opportunity to you to opt-in or opt-out of any such disclosures.

2go may share anonymous personal user information or user activity data with third parties for various reasons, for instance to analyse and better understand user data and behaviour, for marketing, advertising, content sales or for improved Service functionality. 

Any personal information may be used or released by 2go if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with any laws and/or any agreement or other legal rights of 2go or our users, or to protect and ensure the personal safety and information of 2go or 2go users.

If you choose not to submit certain personally identifiable information to 2go, we may not provide all or a part of the Service to you.

### GoCredits

GoCredits enables you to purchase chat room credits, content and/or virtual goods on 2go. You can never redeem GoCredits for cash or use it to purchase products or services, other than certain products on the 2go platform. Unused GoCredits expire 6 months after you have purchased them (or any longer period as may be prescribed in any consumer protection law in your country).

### Security and Safeguards

In order to activate your profile and to protect your privacy you must create your own profile name and unique personal identification number ("PIN") that enables you to log in to the 2go Service. Your PIN should be kept private and not disclosed to any person.

Please note 2go does not currently encrypt your messages sent over the Services and you agree that 2go is not responsible for any unauthorised access to your communications by way of interception or monitoring. 2go uses commercially reasonable efforts in keeping your personal information private and secure. We do not however warrant that your personal information may not be removed, disclosed, changed, or deleted by breach of any of such reasonable safeguards. 2go reserves the right to remove from the Service any messages and/or images, for any reason as determined in our discretion, including by reason of sex, violence, language and/or nudity.

2go reserves the right to host personal information on servers in any country of our choice and to transfer such information to any other location from time to time; and the provisions of this notice shall be subject to the laws of any such country.

### Warranties

The Service is provided on an “as is” basis and 2go does not give you any warranties whatsoever and we disclaim as far as possible all warranties that operate by law. 2go shall not be liable to you for any loss, costs, expenses or damages, including, without limitation, any loss of profit or revenue, or any indirect, special, consequential or punitive damages suffered as a result of your use the Service. You indemnify 2go from any and all liability arising from your failure to adhere strictly to this notice.

### Advertising

2go may display advertisements to you and/or allow advertisers, ad servers or ad networks to serve advertisements to you within the 2go Service. In doing so, we may provide such parties with aggregated anonymous information about you, which would help target specific advertisements to you. 2go and/or such parties may also receive your IP address and also use other technologies to track and analyse the effectiveness of any advertisements. 

### Minimum Age

If you are below the age of 13 you are not allowed to use the 2go Service. 2go does not allow users under the age of 13 to join the Service and we do not knowingly receive and keep personal information from persons under 13 years of age. We reserve the right to remove any profile and/or deactivate any account of any user, including any user less than 13 years of age. 

### Merger, Liquidation or Sale

In the event that 2go is sold, merged or otherwise liquidated your personal information may be transferred and/or assigned to the relevant party or parties concerned.

### Notice Amendments

Your continued use of the Service constitutes your agreement to this Notice and any future amendments. This Notice may be changed from time to time, which will reflected by the "Date Last Amended" below.

Date Last Amended: This Notice was last amended on 16 September 2014.

**2go Interactive (Pty) Ltd**
